Rob Letts

Front-End Web Developer

Email: roblettsdev@gmail.com

Phone: +447449983319 Location: London, UK GitHub: rob-letts LinkedIn: robertletts

Site: robletts.dev



 HTML



SVG



CSS



SCSS



TailwindCSS



JavaScript



TypeScript



Vue.js



Vite



Nuxt



Vitest



Cypress

Bio

Front-End Web Developer based in South London, specialising in modern CSS, design systems, and the Vue ecosystem.

Advocate for universal accessibility and utilising platform standards to sustainably further positive web experiences.

Conscious and empathetic individual that prioritises open communication and empowering colleagues. Previous career in live events and music venue management.

Employment

TixTrack - Senior Front End Engineer

October 2024 - Present

TixTrack - Front End Engineer

June 2022 - October 2024

UI/UX and Design System specialist within a Front End Team migrating and extending an existing Angular monolith to a new Vue architecture, for international ticketing solutions for live events and museums - primarily for Broadway NYC and London's West End theatres.

Red Snapper - Junior Front-End Web Developer

October 2021 - June 2022

Using Vue.js, SCSS, and TailwindCSS to implement dynamic UIs for Laravel and in-house CMS back-ends, as well as standalone microsites, for the London-based web design and development agency offering web implementations and consultancy for a variety of clients, including the BBC and British Medical Journal.

Corsica Studios - Assistant General Manager

March 2012 - November 2020

Overseeing teams of up to 50 to ensure safe running of live music events for crowds of 1000+. Co-ordinating and engineering audio-visual equipment and technical requirements for international musicians and artists, as well as training and developing staff.

Education

MSc, Computer Science - Distinction

September 2020 - September 2021

Birkbeck, University of London

BA (Hons), Music and Sonic Media - Merit

September 2010 - June 2013

London South Bank University